- GUARD: You two! Over here!
你们俩，过来！
Get those two girls over to
the main administration building! Move!
把这两个女孩儿带到主行政大楼去！动起来！
- Zoe and Isobel.
- Wait. We'll follow in a few moments.
- 是 Zoe 和 Isobel  - 等等， 我们一会儿再跟上
Take them inside. Central block, tenth floor.
带她们进去。中央区域，10楼
(ROTORS WHIRRING)
Could be the Brigadier's lot.
Call them up for help.
可能是准将的人。请求他们帮助
No, no, not yet.
We've got to rescue the girls first.
不，不，先不要。我们得先把这两姑娘救出来
Tenth floor, central block. Come on.
10楼，中央区域。快点
There's a lot of unusual activity, sir.
Guards everywhere.
有很多异常活动，长官。到处都是警卫
It looks like some sort of emergency.
看起来像是某种紧急状况
BRIGADIER: Any sign of the Doctor and the boy?
有博士和那个男孩儿的踪迹吗？
No, sir. None at all.
没有，长官。完全没有
Right,Jimmy. Get out of the area and stand by.
好，Jimmy。撤离那个区域，待命
Right, sir. Will do.
收到，长官。马上执行
- All units, please, Sergeant.
- Yes, sir.
- 请接所有小组，军士  - 是，长官
Go ahead, sir.
开始吧，长官
This is the Brigadier. All units, stand by.
我是准将。所有小组，准备
Full penetration of red sector imminent.
即将切入红区fixme
Hey, Zoe.
嘿，Zoe
Zoe, look!
Zoe, 看！
- Doctor!  - Jamie!
- 博士！  - Jamie!
Yes, Doctor, come in.
是的，博士，进来
Brigadier, I think we shall require
a little assistance in a few moments.
准将，我想再过一小会儿我们需要一点援助
Are you in trouble?
你们遇到麻烦了？
No, but we shall need help.
You have a helicopter in the area?
还没有，但我们需要帮助。你在这个区域有直升机吧?
Yes.
是的
I wonder, have they a rope ladder on board?
我在想，他们那里有绳梯吗？
Yes, I'm pretty sure they have. Where are you?
是的，我非常肯定他们有。你们在哪里？
We're just going up to the roof
of the main building.
我们正要上到主楼的楼顶去
That is the central block on the north side.
主楼在北边的中央区域
That should give your helicopter cover
should there be any ground fire.
那个位置可以让直升机安全一点，万一地面有火力的话
- Have you got that?
- Yes, I've got that.
- 你明白了吗？  - 是的，我明白了
Over and out.
完毕，挂断
You were lucky, dead lucky.
你们很幸运，非常幸运
He said it would be
a simple rescue operation. Simple.
他说将是一个简单的营救行动。简单
But what about my uncle?
但我的叔叔怎么样了？
- They've still got him prisoner.
- Don't worry, Miss Watkins.
- 他还是他们的囚徒  - 别担心，Watkins 小姐
As soon as we return to base,
I'm going to raise hell and get some action.
等我们一回到基地，我就增派人手fixme，展开一些行动
You think they'll listen to you now?
你觉得他们现在会听你的了？
No one, not even Tobias Vaughn, can go as far
as trying to shoot down one of my helicopters.
没人能够猖狂到想把我的直升飞机打下来，就算 Tobias Vaughn 也不行
Oh, I wish I'd had my camera.
I could have got a fortune for those pictures.
噢，我期望我待了摄像头。我本来有可能拍到一些镜头的fixme
Yes, it was a pity.
是的，真比较遗憾
That would have clinched it
as far as the Ministry are concerned, sir.
fixme
Don't worry, Jimmy. Billy Rutlidge
will have to take some action now.
别担心, Jimmy。Billy Rutlidge 现在必须采取些行动了
Why am I being taken back to London?
为什么把我带回伦敦？
What about my niece? What's happened to Isobel?
我的侄女怎么样了？Isobel 她发生了什么？
I tell you, she's perfectly safe.
我告诉你，她相当安全
Well, I want to see her!
那，我想要见她！
So you shall.
那你会的
When you've finished working on your machine.
只要你先完成那台机器
Do as I ask and you shall both go free.
按我要求的做，你们俩都可以得到自由
You don't even expect me to believe you, do you?
你没指望我会相信你吧，是吗
Well, you've very little choice.
只是，你的选择很少
Now, we're going back to London.
现在，我们要回到伦敦
There you will work on your machine
to my specifications.
你在那里要按我定的规格做出那台机器
You will have 24 hours to complete it.
你有24小时来完成这项任务
Only if you haven't finished your work by that time
只有你到那时还没有完成你的工作
would you have cause to worry about your niece.
你才有理由担心你的侄女
- BRIGADIER: Mean anything to you, Doctor?
- Possibly.
- 让你想起什么吗，博士？  - 可能吧
How long ago were these objects first sighted?
第一次看见这些东西是在多久以前？
Reports have been drifting in
for well over a year now.
一年多以前就有报告送来了
We sent up fighter planes to investigate,
but nothing ever came of it.
我们派了战斗机去调查，但没有任何结果
The odd thing about these sightings is
这些目击事件比较奇怪的地方是，
that they usually seem to disappear
somewhere over southeast England.
它们似乎通常都消失在英格兰的东南部某处
But isn't that where all those factories
and laboratories of Vaughn's are?
但那不是 Vaughn 的工厂和实验室都在那边吗？
Exactly.
的确
Well, obviously they bring these things,
whatever they are..
那，显然是他们把这些东西，不管它们是什么...
up from the factory in the country
to the London premises.
从乡村的工厂带到了伦敦市区
That's where we're going to find the answer.
那就是我们要求找寻答案的地方
You mean go back to Vaughn's place?
你是说回到 Vaughn 的地盘去？
I don't think that's wise, Doctor.
You've been lucky so far.
我觉得那样并不明智，博士。你们目前已经够幸运的了
Aye, if you think I'm going back inside there...
是。如果你觉得我打算回到那里面去...
Jamie, we have to find what is inside these crates.
Jamie，我们必须搞明白那个板条箱里面是什么
Brigadier, have you got a map,
including the London premises?
准将，你有地图吗，包含伦敦市区的？
- Yes, yes, I think so. Sergeant Walters!
- Sir?
- 有， 有，我想是有。Walters 军士!  - 长官！
- Jamie, I'm afraid I was right!
- Eh?
- Jamie，恐怕我说对了  - 呃？